- [DIRECTOR] PLAYBACK!
(UPBEAT HIP HOP)
(CROWD CHEERING)
♪ 1989! ♪
♪ THE NUMBER, ANOTHER SUMMER ♪
♪ SOUND OF THE FUNKY DRUMMER ♪
♪ MUSIC HITTIN' YOU HEART
'CAUSE I KNOW YOU GOT SOUL ♪
♪ BROTHERS AND SISTERS ♪
♪ HEY, HEY ♪
♪ LISTEN IF YOU'RE
MISSIN', Y'ALL ♪
♪ SWINGIN' WHILE I'M SINGIN' ♪
♪ GIVIN' WHAT YOU'RE GETTIN' ♪
♪ KNOWIN' WHAT I KNOWIN' ♪
♪ WHILE THE BLACK
BAND'S SWEATIN' ♪
♪ AND THE RHYTHM
RHYMES ROLLIN' ♪
♪ GOT TO GIVE US WHAT WE WANT ♪
♪ GOTTA GIVE US WHAT WE NEED ♪
♪ OUR FREEDOM OF SPEECH
IS FREEDOM OF DEATH ♪
♪ WE GOT TO FIGHT
THE POWERS THAT BE ♪
♪ FIGHT THE POWER ♪
♪ WE GOT TO FIGHT
THE POWERS THAT BE ♪
♪ AS THE RHYTHM'S
DESIGNED TO BOUNCE ♪
♪ WHAT COUNTS IS
THAT THE RHYME'S ♪
♪ DESIGNED TO FILL YOUR MIND ♪
♪ NOW THAT YOU REALIZE
THE PRIDE'S ARRIVED ♪
♪ WE GOT TO PUMP THE
STUFF TO MAKE US TOUGH ♪
♪ FROM THE HEART, IT'S
A START, A WORK OF ART ♪
♪ TO REVOLUTIONIZE, MAKE A
CHANGE, NOTHING'S STRANGE ♪
♪ PEOPLE, PEOPLE,
WE ARE THE SAME ♪
♪ NO, WE'RE NOT THE SAME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE DON'T
KNOW THE GAME ♪
♪ WHAT WE NEED IS AWARENESS ♪
♪ WE CAN'T GET CARELESS ♪
♪ YOU SAY, WHAT IS THIS? ♪
♪ MY BELOVED, LET'S
GET DOWN TO BUSINESS ♪
♪ MENTAL SELF-DEFENSIVE
FITNESS ♪
♪ DON'T RUSH THE SHOW ♪
♪ YOU GOTTA GO FOR
WHAT YOU KNOW ♪
♪ MAKE EVERYBODY SEE, ♪
♪ IN ORDER TO FIGHT
THE POWERS THAT BE ♪
♪ LEMME HEAR YOU SAY ♪
♪ FIGHT THE POWER ♪
♪ WE'VE GO TO FIGHT
THE POWER THAT BE ♪
(UPBEAT HIP HOP)
(CROWD CHEERING)
♪ FIGHT THE POWER ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT TO FIGHT
THE POWERS THAT BE ♪
♪ ELVIS WAS A HERO TO MOST ♪
♪ BUT HE NEVER MEANT
SHIT TO ME YOU SEE ♪
♪ STRAIGHT OUT RACIST,
THE SUCKER WAS ♪
♪ SIMPLE AND PLAIN ♪
♪ MOTHERFUCKING HIM
AND JOHN WAYNE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I'M BLACK
AND I'M PROUD ♪
♪ I'M READY AND HYPED
PLUS I'M AMPED ♪
♪ MOST OF MY HEROES DON'T
APPEAR ON NO STAMPS ♪
♪ SAMPLE A LOOK BACK
YOU LOOK AND FIND ♪
♪ NOTHING BUT REDNECKS FOR
400 YEARS IF YOU CHECK ♪
♪ DON'T WORRY BE HAPPY ♪
♪ WAS A NUMBER ONE JAM ♪
♪ DAMN IF I SAY IT YOU
CAN SLAP ME RIGHT HERE ♪
♪ GET IT ♪
♪ LETS GET THIS
PARTY STARTED RIGHT ♪
RIGHT ON, C'MON
WHAT WE GOT TO SAY?
♪ POWER TO THE PEOPLE NO DELAY ♪
♪ MAKE EVERYBODY SEE ♪
♪ IN ORDER TO FIGHT
THE POWERS THAT BE ♪
♪ FIGHT THE POWER ♪
♪ WE'VE GOT TO FIGHT
THE POWERS THAT BE ♪
(TRUMPET)
(CROWD CHEERING)
GO FLAVOR, GO FLAVOR, GO FLAVOR!
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
(CROWD CHEERING)
- [CHUCK D] EVERYBODY!
C'MON!
ROCK THE HOUSE!
DO OR DIE!
PREPARE TO DIE!
ROCK THE HOUSE Y'ALL!
YEAH, BOY!
C'MON!
EVERYBODY!
OKAY, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.